George!What are you doing?
George! 你在干什么?
I'm working.
我正在工作.
Don't you hear the alarm?
你没有听到警报吗?
Yes.It's horrible.
Yes. 烦死人了.
Is there any way we can turn it off?
有什么方法 我们能关掉它吗?
Turn it off?
把它关掉?
It's just a drill.
只是个演习.
George,it is an emergency drill.
George, 这是应急演习.
It's important.
这是很重要的.
What do I have to do?
我需要干什么?
It's all here.
都在这儿.
Read the instructions.
读一下须知.
If you discover a fire,call 911.
如果你发现着火, 拨打911.
Give the address. Boston Sheraton Hotel,
提供地址. Boston Sheraton酒店.
39 Dalton Street.
多尔顿(Dalton) 街39号.
They discovered the fire,NuLa.
他们发现火情了, NuLa.
The alarm's already on.What else?
警报已经拉响了. 还有什么?
Don't panic!Shut any open windows.
不要惊慌! 关上任何打开的窗子.
Leave your office.
离开你的办公室.
Shut all the doors behind you.
关上你身后所有的门.
Go to your nearest exit.
去距离你最近的出口.
Do not use the elevator.
不要使用电梯.
Use the stairs.
使用楼梯.
Leave the building.
离开大楼.
Women and children first.
妇女和儿童先走.
It doesn't say that.
它没有说那个.